American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series III. Committees, 1906-2005; 1946-1990 bulk; 36 boxes (53.5 linear feet)
  - Subseries III.A. Membership Committee, 1906-1991; 1959-1990 bulk; 618 folders
    - Member Files, Schwab-Schwenk (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Scocca-Scrutton (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Seal-Seiffert (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Sekiguchi-Sen (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Serabjit-Singh-Shainoff (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Shaklee-Shapiro (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Sharma-Shay (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Sheares-Sheppard (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Sherblom-Shing (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Shiota-Shostak (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Shrago-Shyamala (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Siafaka, Kapadai-Siiteri (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Sikela-Simmons (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Simon-Singer (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Singh-Sivaram (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Sjolander-Slama (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Slate-Sly (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Small-Smith, Eugene (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Smith, Frances-Smith, Michael (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Smith, Peter-Smulson (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Sneider-Sckatch (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Sokoloff-Sonenshein (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Song-Sowokinos (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Member Files, Sparrow-Spychala (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Spies-Spychala (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Squinto-Srivastava (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Starch-Starich (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Stark-Stegink (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Stein-Steitz (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Stellwagen-Stern (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Sternberg-Stewart (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Stiefel-Stollar (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Stone-Stratman (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Straub-Sturman (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Suarez-Sun (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Sundaralingam-Suzuki (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Svanas-Sweet (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Swenson-Szer (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Tabachnick-Tallant (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Tallman-Tavormina (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Taylor, A.-Taylor, W. (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Tedeschi-Tewksbury (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Thach-Thomas, George (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Thomas, James-Thurman (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Tibbetts-Titchener (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Tlsty-Toohey (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Toporek-Townsend (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Traber-Trinkaus (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Tritsch-Trzakos (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Tsai-Tsubokawa (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Tu-Tutwiler (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Twining-Tzagoloff (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Uchida-Ulmer (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Umeda-Uziel (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Vagelos-Van Eldik (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Van Es-Vashington (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Vatsis-Vercesi (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Verjovski-Vessey (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Via-Vitols (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Vladutiu-Vliegenthart (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Vogel-Vydelingum (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Wachsman-Walborg (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Wald-Walsh, Michael (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Walsh, Peter-Wang, Peng (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Wang, Su-San-Warner, Alden (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Warner, Carol-Waxman (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Weaver-Webster, George (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Webster, Leslie-Weinryb (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Weinstein-Weith (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Wejksnora-Westhead (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Wetmur-Whitaker (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, White-Whittaker (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Wiberg-Wiehle (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Member Files,Wiggert-Williams, J. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Wilson, James-Winkler (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Wilson, James-Winkler (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Womstead-Wixom (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Woessner-Wolff, Edith (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Wolff, Jan-Wood, Harland (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Wood, Henry-Woychik (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Wright-Wrogemann (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Wu-Wynn (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Xie-Xu (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Yadav-Yamane (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Yamano-Yang, David (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Yang, Funmei-Yarus (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Ye-Yip (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Yoakum-Yount (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Yphantis-Yuwiler (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Zabrecky-Zaugg (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Zeheb-Zhang (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Zhao-Zipursky (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Zoller-Zyskind (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Subseries III.B. Ad hoc Committees, 1930-1991; 1960-1980 bulk; 19 folders
    - Ad hoc Committee on 50th Anniversary-Correspondence and Miscellaneous Materials, 1954-56 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-laws Revision, The First Twenty-five Years of the American Society of Biological Chemists by Russell H. Chittenden (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-laws Revision, By-laws, 1940s (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1942-46 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Ad hoc Committee on 50th Anniversary-Correspondence, Invitations to Foreign Societies (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1951-59 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-laws Revision, By-laws, 1940s (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, By-laws, 1962-63 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1975-76 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Constitution and By-Laws Revision, Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Industrial Cooperation and Career Recruitment, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Medical Research Funding, Correspondence, 1990/91 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Meetings, Correspondence, 1979/80 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Meetings, Correspondence, 1987/88 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Research Support, Correspondence, 1979, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Reorganization of Historical Documents, Proposal, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Ad hoc Committee on the Quality of the Environment, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Subseries III.C. Armed Forces Committee, 1949-1952; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1949-52 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Subseries III.D. Awards Committee, 1979-2002; bulk 1979-1991; 7 folders
    - Correspondence, 1979-91 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence January-May 1994 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence June 1994 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence July- November 1994 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence 2000 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence 2001 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Howard Schachman Public Service Award, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Subseries III.E. Committee on Biochemical Nomenclature, 1930-1969; bulk 1954-1969; 3 folders
    - Correspondence, 1930, 1932, 1937-39, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1954-64, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1967-69 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Subseries III.F. Committee on Clinical Chemistry, 1948-1968; 4 folders
    - Correspondence, 1948, 1950-51, 1954-61 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Intersociety Committee. on Laboratory Services Related to Health, Correspondence, 1953-58 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1963-68 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III.G. Committee on Equal Opportunities for Minority Groups (Minority Affairs), 1971-2001; bulk 1979-1988; 23 folders
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-July 1973 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence Aug 1973-Dec 1974 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Jan-June 1979 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Aug-Dec 1979 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jan-June 1980 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, July-Dec 1980 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1982-84 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1990-91 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Grant Application to MARC program, 1977-79 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Materials, 1968-1971 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Minority Affairs Correspondence May-October 2001 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Minority Affairs Establishment Documents 1971-1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Minority Affairs Subcommittee on Minority Affairs 1994 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III.H. Committee on Equal Opportunities for Women, 1971-1991; 14 folders
    - Correspondence, 1971-72 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1981-84 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1985-86 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1990-91 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Subseries III.I. Committee on Human Biochemistry, 1969-1975; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1969-75 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Subseries III.J. Committee on Long-Range Goals, 1970-1971; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Subseries III.K. Committee on Plans for Scientific Meetings, 1959-1963; 2 folders
    - Correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1961-63 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Subseries III.L. Committee on Procedures, 1965-1973; 5 folders
    - Correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1/1970-6/1970 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 8/1970-12/1970 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1971-73 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III.M. Committee on Reorganization of Administrative & Business Procedures, 1950-1951; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1950-51 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Subseries III.N. Committee on the Professional Training of Biological Chemists, 1946-1953; 1 folder
    This committee was dissolved in 1953.
    - Correspondence, 1946-53 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III.O. Committee on the Relations of Biochemists to the Reorganization of the Sanitary Corps, 1947-1949; 1 folder
    This committee was dissolved in 1949.
    - Correspondence, 1947-49 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III.P. Educational Affairs Committee, 1959-1994; 57 folders
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1960 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jan-August 1961 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Sept-Dec 1961 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-July 1962 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, August-Dec 1962 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1963 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1964 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1965 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1966 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1967-70 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1971 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1972-73 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence 1974-75 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence 1976-79 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 1980 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence 1981-82 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1984 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1985-86 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1987 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1988 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1989 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1990 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1991-92 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Materials 1980 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Misc. Materials, Mobil Oil, 1980-88 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Agenda 1989 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Agenda 1990 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Agenda 1992 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - American Chemical Society (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Career Opportunities Literature, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1986 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1987 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence 1988 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence 1990 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 1991 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence 1992 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence 1994 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Education Articles 1989 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - EAC/ASBMB Survey 1991 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - FASEB Education Committee 1990 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - FASEB Education Committee 1991 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Fellowships, High School, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fellowships, High School, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Latin American Program: Correspondence 1989 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Latin American Program: Correspondence 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Latin American Program: Correspondence 1992 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Latin American Program: Correspondence 1993 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Latin American Program: Correspondence 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Latin American Program: Finance Committee Report 1994 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Latin American Program: First International Symposium on Sucrose Metabolism (FISSM) 1994 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Latin American Program: Surveys 1988 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Latin American Program: Travel Expense Vouchers 1994 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Member Lists 1987-1991 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Meeting Information 1991 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Minutes 1988-1992 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Travel Vouchers 1994 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Subseries III.Q. Feasibility Committee, 1969-1970; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Subseries III.R. Future of Biochemistry Committee, 1965-1967; 1 folder
    - Arthur Kornberg Correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Subseries III.S. Nominating Committee, 1946-2001; bulk 1960-1990; 20 folders
    - Correspondence, 1946-49 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1950-53 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1954-57 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1958-59 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1960-62 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Alton Meister, Correspondence, 1962-67 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1963-65, 1967-69 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Ad hoc Com. on Governance, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1973-76 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1981-83 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1984-86 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1990-91 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Nominating Com.: Correspondence 1994 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Nominating Com.: Correspondence 1999-2001 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Nominating Com.: Election Results 1994 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Subseries III.T. Past-President's Committee, 1990; 2 folders
    - Correspondence, 1-2/1990 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 3-4/1990 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III.U. Public Affairs Committee and Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1970-2002; bulk 1990-2002; 60 folders
    - Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972-74 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1-6/1980 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 7-12/1980 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1-5/1985 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1-5/1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1-5/1986 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 6-12/1986 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1-4/1987 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 5-12/1987 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1-5/1988 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 6-12/1988 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1-5/1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 6/10/1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 11/12/1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, March 1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 4-6/1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 7-9/1990 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1990 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Public Affairs News, Notes, Peter Farnham, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Subcommittee on Science and Human Rights, 1985-86 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Peter Kyros, 1989-Feb 1990 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Peter Kyros, June 1990-March 1991 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Joint ASBMB/ASCB Oversight Committee, 1991 Folder 15: Misc. Materials 1985 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Materials 1985 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Campaign for Medical Research 2000 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence Jan.-May 1994 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence June-Sept. 1994 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence 2000 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence January 2001 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence Feb.-May 2001 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence June-August 2001 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence Sept.-Dec. 2001 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence January 2002 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence February 2002 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence March-April 2002 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence May 2002 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence May-June 2002 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - FASEB-BIO Meeting 2002 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - News June 1990 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - News August 1990 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Travel Vouchers 1994 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Subseries III.V. Audit Committee, 1980; 1 folder
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III.W. Finance Committee, 1946-2002; bulk 1962-2002; 32 folders
    - Correspondence, 1946, 49-56 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1957-61 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1973-74 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-July, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1981-86 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Finance Report 1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1955, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Minutes, Meeting with Loomis-Sayles and Company, 1961, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1980-81 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1982-83 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1984-85 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1988-89 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agenda, 1990-91 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Financial Statements 1999 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Financial Statements 2000 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Financial Statements 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Minutes 2000 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Subseries III.X. Committee Appointments and Liaison Officers, 1980-1991; 2 folders
    - Committee Appointments and Liaison Officers, 1980-88 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Committee Appointments and Liaison Officers, 1990-91 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Subseries III.Y. Human Relations Subcommittee on Equal Opportunities for Women (EOW), 2001; 2 folders
    - Correspondence 2001 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Travel Vouchers (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Subseries III.Z. Joint Steering for Public Policy Committee (JSPP), 1995-2002; 10 folders
    - Correspondence 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1995 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1997 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1998 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence 1999 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence 2000 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 2001 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence 2002 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Governance 1993 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Minutes 1998 & 1999 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Subseries III.AA Meetings Committee, 1999-2002; 7 folders
    - Agenda 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Committee Member Lists 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence 1999-2000 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence 2001 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence 2002 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Minutes 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - News 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Subseries III.BB Membership Task Force, 2000-2002; 3 folders
    - Advertisements (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Agenda (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Series IV. Meetings, 1906-2002; bulk 1934-2002; 29 boxes (42.35 linear feet)
  - Subseries IV.A. Council/Executive Board Meetings, 1906-2002; bulk 1942-2002; 98 folders
    - Meeting for Organization, New York, 1906 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, First Special Meeting, Washington, 1907; Second Annual Meeting, Chicago, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, Baltimore, 1908 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, Boston, 1909 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1919, 1922; First & Second Business Meeting, 1920, 1921 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1923-1925 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1927-1931 (Box 66, Folder 7)